[Music]
in this video i would like to share
a little bit about moving to the
countryside
i know that many are curious as to the
steps that i took to make this happen
and i will be sharing more about that on
my instagram page in order to get into
the details
but in short the answers to those
questions are simple
no i'm not wealthy and yes i have to
work hard to be able to live here
it isn't easy and living rurally comes
with its own set of struggles
the opportunity to work here as a
teacher was offered to me about two
years ago
but at the time i wasn't sure whether or
not to take it
i had a life and job as a clerk and
while my environment suited my siblings
who both live in cities
my spirit was restless it was cathartic
when i realized that that was not where
i was meant to be
also that i was terrified of change
that was the hard part stepping into the
unknown taking the risk that things
might not work out with my job
finances and long-term sense of
fulfillment
but i think that's true for many things
in life the first
step is by far the hardest
[Music]
do
for the sake of context my father works
in the military
and consequently i grew up moving from
place to place
by the time i was 20 i'd lived in
several countries and was
pretty well traveled moving here was
terrifying because i couldn't imagine
being somewhere without inevitably
leaving it
but there was something about this place
and i knew i'd found my home
if i could give only one piece of advice
to anyone seeking to live in the
countryside
it is to come here with intention in
these parts of the world where nature is
thriving
you are a steward and must seek to live
in alignment with your surroundings
that involves learning about your local
habitats and animals
and how your choices directly impact
them
in this day and age we must live by this
philosophy that by being here we are
representatives and protectors
of course no matter where you live you
can adopt this philosophy
as well
[Music]
do
for example my town has come together to
defend their home when mining companies
wish to take advantage of natural
resources
if there had been no humans here it
could have happened without even making
the news
work parties pick up the garbage that
accumulates on the roads after tourist
season
many make efforts to control the spread
of noxious weeds
by scanning their properties every year
it's not easy to live out here
and it comes with great responsibility
[Music]
i seek to give my love to the earth in
any way
i can even though my relationship always
has room for improvement
but that's why i came here to learn
now that autumn is in full swing the
rain has come to my valley and i am so
grateful for it it is a blessing on this
earth
and i wanted to go out and witness it
myself
so
[Music]
my favorite place to experience the
rainfall is in the mountains
but as i climbed i realized that
something much more exciting was in
store
and that was one of the first snowfalls
of the season
it was so magical that i simply had to
take you along
you